Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG.37.4
New York University Archives
- Series III. Audio and Video Recordings, 1974-2010
  - Subseries IIIA. Cassette Tapes, 1974-2005
    - Mid-19th Century Urban American Commercial Culture, circa 1986; cuid4197; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 95 minutes; Insert label: Betsy Blackmar/Commercial Culture Seminar
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 103)
      - Access Copies (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:39-11:40)
    - Carol Vance, Undated; cuid4198; 1 audiocassettes (Box 72, Folder 104)
      Physical Technical notes
      During the process of digitization of this collection, it was found that the content on this tape is so faint as to be virtually non-existent. For this reason, it was not transferred to a digital medium at this time. The tape will be retained as part of the collection and perhaps at some point in the future, technology will become available to access the content of the recording.
      Content is so faint that it is nearly inaudible and cannot be discerned.
    - Russian Avant-Garde and Abstract Painters, circa 1979-1981; cuid4199; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 56 minutes
      Physical/Technical
      Recorded on both sides of a TDK Normal Bias, D-C90 audiocassette, manufactured between 1979 and 1981.
      George Costakis discusses the history of Russian art and artists from the late 19th and early 20th centuries. He touches on Russian avant-garde and abstract movements and includes artists such as Alexander Rodchenko and Wassily Kandinsky. He mentions feeling empathetic toward contemporary art movements in Poland because of the Soviet imposed government, indicating the recording was made sometime during the Cold War. Given the year of the tape's manufacture, it was likely the mid-late 1970s.
      Russia.; Art.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); Kandinsky, Wassily, 1866-1944; Costakis, Georgi; Rodchenko, Aleksandr Mikhaĭlovich, 1891-1956
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 105)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:41)
    - Poverty and Economics Through the Religious Lens, Undated; cuid4200; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 34 minutes; Insert Label: NYIH - Same Bowles No. 2
      Economist Samuel Bowles examines poverty and economics through a religious and philosophical lens, referring specifically to Latin American poverty. He also touches on the work of Gustavo Gutiérrez.
      Recorded on one side of a Maxell UR 90, Position-IEC Type I, Normal audiocassette, manufactured between 1985-86.
      Latin America.; Latin America -- Economic conditions.; Economics.; Economic development |z Latin America.; Economic assistance, American |z Latin America.; Bowles, Samuel; Gutiérrez, Gustavo, 1928
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 106)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:42)
    - Brazil Classics Vol. 1: Beleza Tropical (Various Artists), October 1989; cuid4201; 1 audiocassettes (Box 72, Folder 107)
      This is actually a commercially released compilation album entitled "Brazil Classics, Vol. 1: Beleza Tropical." Full of Latin and Tropicalia songs by artists such as Milton Nascimento and Nazare Pereira, this album was compiled by the Talk Heads front man David Byrne and released in October of 1989.
      Brazil.
    - On the South African Apartheid System, cuid4202; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 53 minutes; Tape Label: "Breyten Breytenbach - Speaks of the South African apartheid system." The recording volume is very low, making it difficult to hear in some places. There is also microphone noise every now and then.
      Recorded on both sides of a TDK Normal Bias 120 us EQ D90 Audiocassette, manufactured between 1982 and 1984.
      South African painter and writer discusses the system of South African Apartheid.
      Apartheid; South Africa; Breytenbach, Breyten
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 108)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:43)
    - New Directorial Methods for King Lear, circa 2003-2004; cuid4203; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 64 minutes; Tape label: VIP LECTURE 2. The volume begins to fade about 36 minutes into the recording on Side 1. The volume comes back up somewhat on side 2 but then fades again. Strangely, the level of the background noise does not vary. Ordinarily this would indicate the distance of the speaker to the microphone was increasing, however, there is nothing in the content (mic noises, or ambient clunks) ordinarily associated with mic movement.
      British theater director and actor Jonathan Miller discusses his upcoming production of King Lear at Lincoln Center in New York City. He speaks directly for about 15 minutes and then engages in Q&A with the audience.
      Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616. King Lear.; Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts; Miller, Jonathan, 1934-2019; Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 109)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:44)
    - Depiction of Fashion and Dress in Early Cinema, Undated; cuid4204; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 89 minutes; Insert Label: Censorship Seminar 2/25, SCAMMEL Tape Label: Censorship Seminar, Scammell, 2/25 [second digit of date unclear) There is an audio artifact at the beginning of the recording. It sounds like a squeaky cog inside the tape recorder.
      This tape is labeled "Censorship Seminar 2/25, SCAMMEL," which may have been referencing a talk given by author and translator Michael Scammell during the February 25 session of the NYIH 1982 Censorship Seminar. However, on listening to the tape, the content is of a discussion and slideshow lead by art historian Anne Hollander. Hollander, an art historian whose focus is on the pictorial depiction of dress and fashion in works of art throughout history discusses fashion and clothing in early cinema.
      Related Materials
      Other recordings from the Censorship Seminar are located in Box 39, folders 13 and 14.
      Fashion -- History; Film.; Fashion; Fashion in art; Silent films; Hollander, Anne
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 110)
      - Access Copies (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:45-11:46)
    - Live Script Reading of an Unidentified Play, Undated; cuid4205; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 26 minutes; Tape label: "Tape 2, TRIOS, Ed White, 4/29"
      Recording is a section of a play reading. Consists mostly of dialog between a younger man and and older man about their trust or distrust of women. The younger man appears to have feelings for the older man's wife. The younger man is leaving soon for Australia, a trip which will first take him by train and then by ship, indicating that it is a period piece or written during the days of ocean liners. A Google search for quotes from the script yielded no identifying results.
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 111)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:38)
    - Coma and After: The Experience of Consciousness, April 6, 2001; cuid4206; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 66 minutes; Tape label: "Martin Kace on emerging from Coma" Case label: "6 April 2001, Martin Kace, Coma & After"
      Psychologist Martin Kace discusses consciousness and emerging from a coma after a spinal accident that left him paralyzed. He was struck by a falling tree, breaking several vertabrate. He was in a coma for four weeks. He (and his doctor) discuss consciousness and coma from medical, psychological, neurological, and philosophical perspectives.
      Consciousness; Spinal cord -- Wounds and injuries; Paralysis; Loss of consciousness; Kase, Martin
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 112)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:47)
    - Light and Life in Los Angeles, after 1998; cuid4207; Waldie, D.J.; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 63 minutes; Severe electrical hum heard under content; low audio normalization boosted to -3 dB on side 1, and -1 dB on side 2 for the access copy.
      Introduced by Ren Weschler, essayist Don (D.J.) Waldie discusses light, art, and life in Los Angeles. Waldie introduces his topic by referencing a February 1998 New Yorker article written by Weschler, in which he quotes Waldie about the remarkable quality of light in Los Angeles.
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 115)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:23)
    - Jung: A Biography, circa 2004; cuid4208; Bair, Deirdre; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 62 minutes
      Deirdre Bair discusses her most recent (2004) biography, Jung: A Biography.
      Jung, C. G. (Carl Gustav), 1875-1961
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 116)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:24)
    - Visual Memory and Imagery, Undated; cuid4209; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 70 minutes
      Oliver Sacks discusses an inquiry he is working on at the time dealing with visual memory, visual imagery and visualization. He draws on his own experience as a person with Prosopagnosia or face blindness - a brain disorder characterized by the inability to recognize faces.
      Memory; Prosopagnosia; Memory disorders; Sacks, Oliver, 1933-2015
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 117)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:25)
    - Tuscany: Inside the Light, Undated; cuid4210; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 70 minutes
      Husband and wife collaborators, Joel Meyerowitz and Maggie Barrett discuss their work on a photography book about Tuscany, Italy. Meyerowitz also makes references to his creating a photographic historic record of Ground Zero in the wake of the September 11, 2001 terrorist attacks, which he was working on simultaneously. While they started this project in 2001, the book was not published until 2010, making it difficult to date the recording.
      Tuscany (Italy); Italy; Photography; Barrett, Maggie; Meyerowitz, Joel, 1938-
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 118)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:26)
    - River of Shadows: Eadweard Muybridge and the Technological Wild West, circa 2004; cuid4211; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 59 minutes
      Author Rebecca Solnit discusses the work of photographer Eadward Muybridge, paying particular attention to his photos of Native Americans and the Modoc War in the 1870s. She had recently written a book about Muybridge and his work in the American West, entitled River of Shadows: Eadweard Muybridge and the Technological Wild West.
      Modoc Indians -- Wars, 1873; Indians of North America.; Photography; Photography |z United States.; Muybridge, Eadweard, 1830-1904; Solnit, Rebecca
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 120)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:27)
    - Cultural Shock from Traumatic Events, circa 2003; cuid4212; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 67 minutes
      Former NYIH Fellow, Wolfgang Schivelbusch discusses the nature of shock taking into consideration both recent and distant events, specifically referencing the terrorist attacks of September 11, 2001 as well as World War I. He goes into events as "raw events" and then what the media portrays and creates in its wake.
      World War |y 1914-1918 |x History; September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001.; Schivelbusch, Wolfgang
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 121)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:28)
    - New York City Street Photography Slideshow Narration, Undated; cuid4213; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 16 minutes
      Recording of an unidentified speaker narrating a slide show of New York City street photography, apparently in the wake or run-up to the publication of a book of the photos. The speaker makes frequent reference to someone named Alfred who was likely involved in the project, possibly as the writer of the accompanying text.
      Photography; Street photography
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 122)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:29)
    - The Hockney-Falco Thesis, 2004; cuid4214; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 68 minutes
      Physicist Charles M. Falco discusses his collaboration with British painter David Hockney. Together they created the Hockney-Falco thesis, which proposed that "advances in realism and accuracy in the history of Western art since the Renaissance were primarily the result of optical aids such as the camera obscura, camera lucida, and curved mirrors, rather than solely due the development of artistic technique and skill." (Wikipedia)
      Art, Renaissance; Painting, Renaissance; realism (artistic form of expression); Realism in art; Hockney-Falco thesis; Falco, Charles M.; Hockney, David
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 124)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:30)
    - Behind the Times: Inside the New York Times, circa 1995; cuid4215; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 59 minutes
      Journalist and author Edwin Diamond discusses his recently published book, Behind the Times: Inside the New York Times.
      Journalism; Diamond, Edwin; New York Times Company
      - Original Recording (Box 74, Audiocassette 125)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:31)
    - Freud and Foucault, Undated; cuid4216; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 19 minutes
      This recording appears to be the very end of a seminar or round table discussion about sexuality and Freudian principles in the work of Foucault.
      Sexuality; Foucault, Michel, 1926-1984; Freud, Sigmund, 1856-1939
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 126)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:32)
    - Unidentified Live Opera Performance, Undated; cuid4217; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 32 minutes
      Undated recording of an unidentified live opera performance.
      Opera.
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 127)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:33)
    - Inventing Times Square - Unknown Session, circa 1988-1989; cuid4218; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 33 minutes
      Unidentified speakers discuss various aspects of cultural perception and interpretation of Times Square. This is likely from one of the Inventing Times Square Symposium sessions which took place between 1988 and 1989.
      Times Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 129)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:34)
    - A Discussion with Jon Robin Baitz about His Work, 2002; cuid4219; 1 audiocassettes Approx. 60 minutes
      Jon Robin Baitz discusses his projects and process in writing both films and plays. Recorded on the day after the release of Baitz's 2002 film, People I Know, Baitz specifically delves into what inspired this story.
      Art.; Screenplays; People I know (Motion picture); Baitz, Jon Robin, 1961-
      - Original Recording (Box 72, Audiocassette 132)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:35)
    - Narrative Seminar: Peter Brooks, November 20, 1984 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0001)
    - Narrative Seminar: Dennis Donoghue, December 4, 1984 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0002)
    - Narrative Seminar, February 13, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0003, 37-4.0004)
    - Narrative Seminar, February 20, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0005, 37-4.0006)
    - Narrative Seminar, February 27, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0007, 37-4.0008)
    - Narrative Seminar: B. H. Smith, March 5, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0009)
    - Narrative Seminar, March 6, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0010, 37-4.0011)
    - Narrative Seminar, March 13, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0012, 37.4-0013)
    - Narrative Seminar/NYIH Talk: Ted Mooney, March 19, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0014, 37-4.0015)
    - Narrative Seminar, March 20, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0016)
    - Narrative Seminar, March 27, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0017)
    - Narrative Seminar, April 10, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0018)
    - Narrative Seminar, April 17, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0019, 37-4.0020)
    - Narrative Seminar, April 24, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0021, 37-4.0022)
    - Narrative Seminar, May 1, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0023, 37-4.0024)
    - Narrative Seminar, May 8, 1985 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0025, 37-4.0026)
    - Interpretation Seminar, April 8, 1986; The participants of this seminar include: Jolen Searle, Ronald Dworkin, David Richards, Dagmar Searle, Carol Feldman, Jovei Malcolm, Ann Malcolm, Talih Asad, Jerome Bruner, Donald Spruce, Tom Nagle, Ann Hollander, and W. M. Taylor. Names were transcribed from handwritten labels and may have minor spelling mistakes. (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0027, 37-4.0028)
    - Dark Garland -- Affirming Flame: Leaves from My Commonplace Book by Lawrence Weschler, September 21, 2001 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0029)
    - David Hockney Symposium: Opening Session: Talks by David Hockney and Charles Falco, December 1, 2001 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0030, 37-4.0031, 37-4.0032)
      Three copies of the same recording.
    - David Hockney Symposium: Panel #1: General Perspectives, December 1, 2001 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0033, 37-4.0034, 37-4.0035)
    - David Hockney Symposium: Panel #2: Scientific Vantages, December 1, 2001 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0036, 37-4.0037, 37-4.0038)
    - David Hockney Symposium: Panel #3: Experts on Individual Artists, December 1, 2012 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0039, 37-4.0040)
      Two copies of the same recording.
    - David Hockney Symposium: Panel #4: Artist Responses, December 2, 2012 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0041, 37-4.0042, 37-4.0043)
    - David Hockney Symposium: Panel #4 end, Panel #5: Wider Perspectives, December 2, 2001 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0044, 37-4.0045, 37-4.0046)
    - David Hockney Symposium: Panel #5 end, Closing Remarks by David Hockney and Charles Falco, December 2, 2001 (Box 79, Audiocassette 37-4.0047, 37-4.0048, 37-4.0049)
    - Jan Gross: Revisiting Polish-Jewish relations in the Wake of His Book, "Neighbors", September 28, 2001 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0050)
    - Carina Perelli: On East Timor and Other Adventures in Nation Building, October 5, 2001 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0051)
    - Internal Seminar: The Current Crisis September 11 2001: The Economy, Hosted by Richard Sennett, October 9, 2001 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0052)
    - Robert Krulwich: Panic in the Newsroom (Part II), October 12, 2001 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0053)
    - Jonathan Bush: Telford Taylor, Nuremberg Professor, October 26, 2001 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0054)
    - Leon Botstein: Thoughts on the History of Listening, November 9, 2001 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0055)
    - Internal Seminar: Thoughts on the Current Crisis: Jonathan Schell, November 15, 2001 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0056)
    - Susan Sontag on Regarding the Pain of Others, November 16, 2001 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0057)
    - Helen Epstein on The Plagues of Transition, December 7, 2001 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0058)
    - The Good Old Days, February 27, 2003 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0059)
    - Us vs. Them: Introduction and Panel 1: American Exceptionalism, October 23, 2004 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0060)
    - Us vs. Them: Panel 1: The Islamic Horizon, October 24, 2004 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0061)
    - Us vs. Them: Panel 2: Constitutional Separation of Church and State, October 23, 2004 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0062)
    - Us vs. Them: Panel 2: Wider Perspectives, October 24, 2004 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0063)
    - Us vs. Them: Panel 3: Conversation between Weschler, Vowell, and Kushner, October 23, 2004 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0064)
    - Us vs. Them: Panel 4: Religious and Philosophical Vantages, October 23, 2004 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0065)
    - Us vs. Them: Panel 5: Scientific Vantages (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0066)
    - Whut's Up When Birds Sing Symposium, April 16, 2005 (Box 80, Audiocassette 37-4.0067, 37-4.0068, 37-4.0069, 37-4.0070, 37-4.0071, 37-4.0072, 37-4.0073, 37-4.0074, 37-4.0075, 37-4.0076)
      Five copies of Tape 1 (37-4.0067 - 37-4.0071) and five copies of Tape 2 (37-4.0072 - 37-4.0076).
  - Subseries IIIB. 1/4 Inch Reels, 1976-1991
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later I, 27-29 Sep 1979; cuid4220 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later I, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4221 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Poetry Reading I, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4222 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Poetry Master, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4223 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4224 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later I-III, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4225 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years I-IV, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4226 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later I-V, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4227 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4228 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4229 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II-II, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4230 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II-III, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4231 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II-V, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4232 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later III, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4233 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later IV, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4234 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Tape 4, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4235 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later CIV, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4236 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later E4, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4237 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later 5, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4238 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Session 2 - Culture, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4239 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later - Day 2, Tape 1, September 27-29, 1979; cuid4240
      During digitization and rehousing a list of academic papers on which the Conference was based was found in the case of this tape. A new folder was created and given a unique identifier (ref3081) within Series II of this collection to house the list. It is titled "The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later," (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Original Recording (Box 74, Quarter inch audio reel 12)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Cd 9:47)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Day 2 Tape 2, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4241 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Day 2 Tape 3, September 27-29, 1979; cuid4242
      - Original Recording (Box 74, Quarter inch audio reel 10)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Cd 9:48)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Day 2 Tape 4, September 27-29, 1979; cuid4243
      - Original Recording (Box 74, Quarter inch audio reel 11)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Cd 9:49)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Day 2 Tape 5, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979; cuid4244 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Thursday Night, 1979; cuid4245 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Unlabeled, undated; cuid4246 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Jane Kramer, 7-May-81; cuid4247 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Justin Kaplan -The Art of Biography, 2-Apr-81; cuid4248 (Box 71, Folder 12)